[KAZUMA] A princess, huh?
Sounds like she's probably
younger than I am.
Well, who knows?
If we make friends,
maybe she'll call me
"Big Brother!"
- [DARKNESS] Uh, Kazuma.
- Huh.
W-why not reconsider this?
You should just pass
on their offer. Please?
The nation's most important
people will be there!
All right, that's it,
I've had enough!
You already shot down my idea
of entertaining them
in a traditional kimono
and hakama!
You wanted to "entertain"
royalty in clothes
they have never heard of!
Listen to me.
I am willing to wear this
til the princess arrives
and that is why I expect you
to dress in a proper manner!
Shut your hole!
I don't wanna hear anything
but, "Very good, Master!"
[whimper]
Yes, very good, Master,
please forgive me.
After all, I am nothing
but a lowly sow.
I'm pretty sure
I didn't say all that.
[indistinct chatter]
[sighs] Thank you,
I feel so much more relaxed
wearing these clothes.
The only reason
I said you could
is cause you were
beggin' and cryin'.
You do realize
I am a noble, right?
So, I could never go around...
Caught you grinnin' when you
thought no one could see.
Did not!
Hey, you two
don't start lagging behind.
Relax, don't worry so much.
Just gotta wrap up this deal
before we see the princess.
[WIZ] They all came in
a few moments ago!
The new products
that Kazuma designed, himself!
Of course, if it wasn't
for my assistance,
they would've
never been completed!
Yeah, yeah, sure.
Even though they're
convenient tools from my home.
[munching]
[all gasp]
Impressive that is convenient!
Something like this
is bound to sell, Kazuma!
I'm proudest of the one
that's modeled
after the Destroyer!
Flint and strikers will be
a thing of the past, now.
So I could definitely
use one, too.
[WIZ]
You're welcome to take one.
[MEGUMIN] Me too,
I want to have one, as well!
[giggle]
Why is everyone getting
so excited?
I mean, they're only lighters.
- [AQUA] Well, maybe I'll...
- [thumps]
What the heck was that?
I want to pick a lighter, too.
Sorry Aqua,
but you've gotta pay.
Huh, are you kidding me?
The rest of 'em get to pick
any one they want
so why can't I have a lighter?
Because you didn't lift
a single finger!
Megumin took the time
to help put 'em together!
Darkness got things moving
by hookin' me up
with a major wholesaler!
And what did you do?
Nap all day at the mansion!
If you want a share,
go out and drum up
some business or something!
[whimpers]
- [door opens]
- [screams]
You're such
a good-for-nothing, Kazuma!
And here I was to be quiet
about your little habit
of sniffing our dirty laundry!
Well, those days are over,
you understand me?
You're nothing but an ingrate!
I think everyone
gets the point here!
Stop looking at me like that!
[indistinct chatter]
[AQUA] And, now,
for my next trick,
I'll take what seems
to be just a regular,
run-of-the-mill handkerchief
and then from nowhere
make white doves appear!
[crowd gasping]
Oh man, what is she even doing?
Did she forget
why she's out there?
More! Do some more tricks
like that one!
Yeah, and make it even wilder!
That's okay, you can keep
all your donations.
Please, I'm not
a professional entertainer,
so you don't need to throw me
all your coins.
[MAN 02-D (M)] Don't say that!
Let us reward
your amazing performance!
Listen up, woman!
First, you sprayed
some holy water on the street
and this establishments
doorknob.
Now you're just
resorting to obstructing
the place entirely, huh?
Why don't you mind
your own business, stupid mask?
This happens to be
a public street.
What's so wrong with putting
on a show for these people?
[VANIR]
Stop your incessant rambling!
This is a crucial day for us!
We're launching a new product!
I'm putting an end
to your sabotage!
- [WIZ] Everyone!
- Huh.
A wonderful, brand new item
was just delivered
to our store, today
and I'd love to demonstrate it
for each one of you!
[KAZUMA] Woah, Wiz is acting
like a real business owner!
[AQUA]
Hey, let go of me, Darkness!
These people are ready
for another show!
Thank you so much!
Please, come back again
soon, okay?
So, that'll be two lighters
and a Vanir mask, then?
[WIZ] Sure, coming right up!
[laughing]
You have my renewed thanks,
boy who's quite anxious
at the lack of new developments
after a promising encounter
with a friend
while on vacation!
Yeah, whatever,
just shut up, man!
I am not anxious at all,
understand me!
And you need to quit
lookin' at me like that!
[gasps]
What are you talking about?
I wasn't doing any such thing!
Get a grip, and don't lose
your composure
based on what
some demon tells you!
[VANIR]
Well, more importantly.
At this right I'd say your cut
of three hundred million eris
will be ready
in just a matter of time.
In exchange
for your patience boy,
I offer you this mask.
[KAZUMA] What is that?
[VANIR] It's one of my
mass-produced Vanir Masks.
Put it on during
a moonlit night
to improve your magic power,
blood circulation,
and complexion!
It'll keep you
at the very top of your game!
As if that weren't enough,
yours happens to be
a rare, black redeco.
Soon, every child
will envy you!
[laughs]
[KAZUMA]
Something happened that day
I never imagined I'd see.
Business was really boomin'
at Wiz's store.
And then, at last.
[grunt]
All right, ladies
d'ya know what to do?
Absolutely!
I can blow their minds
with all my best party tricks.
That way, Darkness
is sure to be proud of us!
As for me, I'll make
an awe-inspiring entrance
to surprise the princess!
Kazuma, you have
any idea where I could get
my hands on fireworks
and explosive smoke?
[KAZUMA] I've got
a bad feeling about this.
- [door opens]
- Huh.
[DARKNESS] Everyone.
I must say,
it is my great pleasure,
as Lalatina Dustiness-Ford
to serve as your hostess
for today.
[chuckles]
- [Megumin gasping]
- Ooh, Darkness...
[Kazuma groaning]
[AQUA] Hey, this is feeling
pretty baggy.
Don't you have
something more fitted?
Uh, well, what can I tell you?
A Crusader does need
to have some muscles.
[gasps] Is something
wrong, Megumin?
[grunts]
Hm.
[groans]
I put the dress on
and it falls right off of me.
Could I get a smaller one?
Oh, uh, yes,
that might be possible
but that dress was from back
when I was a little girl, so...
[screaming]
[DARKNESS] Oh, be careful!
Please do not pull my braids!
Wait, what are those things?
They look like smoke bombs
and explosive potions
for chasing away monsters!
Hand them over!
[Megumin screams]
Well, what do you think?
Cute?
Oh!
Hm. Mm.
Uh, hey,
why are you staring
at me like that?
[chuckles]
Okay now, listen.
You must be on your
best behavior in there.
Just one out-of-place comment
and it could cost you
your head.
Um, is there something wrong?
Look, I should
let you guys know.
If they end up wanting
to keep me around,
then I'm gonna need
to move out.
And I don't see any other
way around it, honestly.
That's just how it is,
so prepare yourselves.
Exactly how far along
has this fantasy progressed
inside that brain of yours?
[DARKNESS] Here's the plan.
I will entertain Princess Iris
while the rest of you
enjoy the meal
and nod along, respectfully.
All right, show time!
[door opens]
♪
[DARKNESS] Apologies
for the wait, Princess Iris.
At this time, I would like
to present my friends
and fellow adventurers
Kazuma Satou and his party.
[KAZUMA] Well, I'll be damned.
Something in this world
isn't a total disappointment.
That's a first.
[DARKNESS] Everyone,
this is the first princess
of the kingdom
Iris Stylish-Sword Belzerg.
Please introduce yourselves
with grace and respect.
♪
I am an arch priest
whose named Aqua.
This is truly an honor.
A pleasure to make
your acquaintance.
[chuckles]
And now I'd like to favor you
with my new party trick.
Please pardon me!
I just need to have
a word with my friend!
Hey, let go of me!
I was gonna show 'em
my best illusion!
[Kazuma gasps]
My name is Megumin, Princess,
finally, we're meet...
[screams]
[indistinct yelling]
[KAZUMA] I've gotta say.
That really
is one cute princess!
It seems like
she's bashful, too.
Listen Commoner.
That is no way for someone
like you to gaze upon royalty.
Lower your head
and make no eye contact.
The princess demands that
you offer your introduction
and tales of adventures
quickly.
[KAZUMA] Oh, I see.
[sighs]
I'm good!
[DARKNESS] Princess Iris,
my friends are too nervous
to behave properly!
One moment please!
How unbelievably
cretinous can you be?
What is wrong with you?
I thought I had made myself
perfectly clear!
Ah, back off! I'm the one
who's disappointed here!
I thought I was gonna
meet a real princess!
What the hell's goin' on?
I was expecting her
to say stuff like,
"Oh, I truly love hearing
all about the outside world.
Oh, brave adventurer,
please regale me
with tales
of your valiant exploits!"
You know that kinda crap!
This is her idea
of a great dinner party?
Does she think I'm stupid?
[AQUA] Finished!
- Huh.
[blowing]
♪
[AQUA] I want to offer this
in honor of our meeting.
I even managed to capture
your unruly bed hair,
cause I wanted to get
every last detail.
[groans]
Huh. [screams]
Princess Iris, let me
throw these insolent fools
out for you!
[AQUA] Hey, I'm sorry.
Seriously.
Calm down, okay?
I just, uh...
[CLAIRE] "After seeing
that impressive sand portrait
created in such
a short amount of time
and witnessing
the taciturn Lalatina
in such a state
of utter frenzy,
I will allow this," she says.
Well, then,
it is now time for dinner.
[cutlery clanking]
- [all munching]
- [Darkness whimpering]
It seems Mitsurugi,
the Hero of the Cursed Sword,
spoke of you.
This piques her interest.
The princess wishes
to hear that tale.
I am rather curious, myself.
Besting somebody like him
must not have been
a simple task.
[munching]
[swallows]
As you wish.
[KAZUMA]
And then I used my wits
to prepare the ultimate trap.
So I decided I would
act as the bait
knowing that it would create
a weakness in Sylvia!
Aah!
[whispering]
[CLAIRE] She says she has
never heard tales of someone
who fights as you do.
And that, normally,
the stories recounted
are all of
undefeatable champions
who slay giant monsters
with superior strength.
[inhales deeply]
Well, if I may say so,
Princess.
The difference could be
that I'm constantly striving
to become greater,
and I do it
by taking on foes I know
are much more powerful
than I am.
[chuckles]
Do you have any clue what this
wannabe hero is talking about?
- [whispers]
-"That's quite remarkable.
So, what kind of work did
you do before adventuring?"
She asked me.
I am interested, myself.
Do tell us.
[groaning]
Before coming to this land
most of my hours
were spent
defending my family's home.
I would sharpen
my skills day after day
doing everything
I possibly could
to protect my home
from any outside threats
despite the lack
of understanding or approval.
It was a miserable
line of work.
I see.
Something like
a castle guard, perhaps?
Whatever the case may be
it appears you also secured
your homeland anonymously.
And there were even demands
that I enter a contract
for three months,
at the very minimum.
So, sometimes things got rough.
- [Iris gasps]
- A contract?
You fought
demonic propositions alone?
[AQUA] You were jobless.
[KAZUMA] I'm not lying, am I?
[CLAIRE]
To defeat Sir Mitsurugi
that would mean...
Kazuma, would it be acceptable
for me to examine
your adventurer card
immediately?
[spitting]
[chuckles]
[KAZUMA] Oh man,
there's no way in hell
I can let them see
my adventurer card!
The second they ask me,
"Where did you learn
a Lich skill?"
I am gonna be so screwed!
As I'm sure you know,
Adventurers don't like
to expose their secrets.
Ah, that's right!
Aqua, weren't you going to
show them your special trick?
I'd say that sand portrait
worked out pretty well,
so I think I'm all done here.
Could I get more
of this bubbly, though?
This stuff is good,
bring it on!
I can keep secrets.
Trust me.
Or, maybe
there's more to it than that.
[KAZUMA] Oh, yeah,
you better believe there is!
My friend is of
the very weakest class.
So, of course,
he is quite embarrassed
to have that exposed.
- Yeah, exactly what she said.
- [gasps]
Between that
and what you said before.
Did you actually
defeat Sir Mitsurugi?
[KAZUMA] Oh, it's not like
I can really admit
to ambushing him and then
taking his cursed sword
with Steal!
- [IRIS] Huh.
- [gasps]
- [whispering]
- [sighs]
[all gasp]
W-well... [sighs]
"It is impossible for me
to believe somebody
from the weakest class
could defeat Sir Mitsurugi.
Therefore, I can only assume
that this is a lie.
He is a sword master
and quite handsome."
says the princess.
And I certainly agree
he is an attractive man.
That's enough, you two!
I can't take this level of...
- [Kazuma shrieks]
- Shut your mouth!
You presume far too much
in the presence of royalty!
[KAZUMA] Here's an idea,
If you don't
wanna be yelled at,
maybe try being
a little less insulting?
I beg your pardon.
It's quite clear, my friend
has no concept of manners.
I hope you will overlook this
on my behalf.
[IRIS] Hm.
[whispering]
[RAIN] "At the request
of the Dustiness family,
who has contributed
so much to this land,
I will ignore his insult.
However,
my mood has been soured."
You will be rewarded
for sharing your adventures.
But, now it is my wish
for the lying man
of the weakest class to leave
this place immediately.
[KAZUMA]
Ouch, that's pretty harsh.
I'm just glad
Darkness saved my ass.
Let's get the hell outta here.
- Hm.
- [sword scraping]
[all gasp]
Enough, Megumin,
what are you doing?
- Please stop it!
- Hey!
[groaning]
[Kazuma gasps] Not good!
Megumin's feelin' bad
for me, now!
There's no way
she's gonna let this slide!
[grunts]
[groaning]
[sighs]
[KAZUMA] Or maybe she will
You had me worried.
I assumed you were
about to go berserk.
They wouldn't get away
with speaking like that
if I were here all by myself.
But I'm not gonna
make any trouble.
Cause I know what
that could mean for you.
Huh.
[chuckles]
Princess Iris.
I must ask you
to withdraw your assertion.
Kazuma is not a liar.
[all gasp]
[DARKNESS] He might exaggerate,
rather often, in fact.
but my friend does not lie.
And true, he may well
be in the weakest class,
but in times of real trouble
there is nobody
that I would rather have
at my side.
Princess Iris.
Please, would you consider
taking back your insult
and offering him an apology?
[CLAIRE] Lady Dustiness!
[gasps]
[groans]
I won't do that!
[IRIS] If he really
is telling us the truth,
then have him explain exactly
how he managed
to defeat Sir Mitsurugi!
And if he cannot do that,
it proves he is nothing
- but a pathetic weakling who...
- [thumps]
[both gasp]
[gasps]
How dare you,
Lady Dustiness!
- [gasps] Wait, please, no!
- [sword slashing]
[both gasp]
♪
[gasps]
[DARKNESS] Princess Iris.
Huh?
[chuckles]
I hope you can
forgive me, truly.
But you mustn't
say those things.
Not about someone
who has achieved so much
and fought so hard.
Also, he does not need
to explain himself
detailing Sir Mitsurugi's loss.
Even if he were
unable to do so,
you would still have no right
to dishonor
my friend like that.
[sighs]
[Megumin chuckles]
[sighs] Fine!
All right, then!
I can't keep
my mouth shut with friends
stickin' their necks out
for me, can I?
It may not be the most
impressive thing ever,
but since you're curious,
I can show you exactly
how I beat him.
- [grunts]
- [gasps]
No, it's all right!
I don't even care about this,
anymore, Claire!
[KAZUMA] What's goin on?
Her whole attitudes changed.
Maybe she's sweeter
than I thought.
I think I will just
leave it at that.
Okay, Kazuma?
I know you can handle yourself.
Damn right I can.
[KAZUMA] I mean, look
at the people I've taken on!
Cursed sword Heroes.
Devil King generals.
Even big-shot bounty hunters!
And I've dealt with em all,
one by one.
First, I'll take that
nasty lookin sword!
So let's do this!
Steal!
[gasps]
All right, now it's time
to show them...
[gasping]
[all gasp]
[KAZUMA] Sorry, you can, uh...
I think these are yours?
[gasps] Huh.
[screams]
[DARKNESS] What in the world
is wrong with you?
Are you capable of doing
anything right, Kazuma?
[KAZUMA] I'm sorry!
I...uh, I apologize.
There is no need.
My arm has already healed.
We can both put this behind us.
But, still...
to heal your wound
without a trace left behind.
Not to mention
your great resilience,
Lady Dustiness.
And your comrade is one of
the famous Crimson Demons.
I can see
how you were able to defeat
the Devil Kings generals
so easily.
[Kazuma gasps]
[CLAIRE]
But Kazuma, on the other hand.
Why am I the only one here
who's still giving
the sketchy looks?
[gasps]
Huh.
[whispers]
[chuckles]
I think that's something
you might be
better off saying yourself.
- [gasps]
- Don't be concerned.
I believe Kazuma
is the type who'll go easy
on a person like you,
Princess Iris.
[KAZUMA] Awesome.
Something tells me
I just got insulted again.
Huh?
♪
Hmm.
I deeply regret
ever calling you a liar.
Sorry.
Hmm.
And if it's all right
could I hear
more about your adventures?
[chuckles]
With pleasure!
♪
[CLAIRE] We'll be returning
to the castle now.
Well, Princess Iris,
I do hope we can speak
again when I visit the capital.
[chuckles]
Goodbye.
I'll see you around someday.
Goodbye, Princess.
[gasps]
Oh, what are you talking about?
Huh?
♪
[whimpering] Huh.
[screams]
♪
[both gasp]
- Princess Iris?
Uh, yeah, so, what is this?
[panting]
I'm so excited!
Now, you can tell me more
about your amazing adventures!
[KAZUMA] Yep,
that's the monarchy for ya.
It seems like they do...
- whatever the hell they want!
- [chuckles]
[HANS] It's been quite
a while, Devil King.
This is Hans,
the Deadly Poison Slime.
I've been spending my time
selling slime detergent
by the River Styx...